ILR School Summer Work Training Experience /3078
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Summer Work Training Experience
1946-1950
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3078
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists mainly of reports and memoranda.
3081818
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4055: James O. Morris Office Files /4148: George W. Brooks Additional Papers 5225: ALES Records 5293: New York State Teachers Association Records 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5786: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5825: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6046: Archives Union File (AUF) 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files 6174/003: NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services. Files 6174/004: NYSUT Field Services Department Files 6414: Interfaith Worker Justice Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
3081818
- Memos, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Memos, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Memos, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Memos and Agreements, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Memos, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  1 Photograph
- Reports and Memos, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Memos, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Memos, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Reports and Memos, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Alleghany Ludlum Steel Corp. Jimmy Umriger, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Avco Manufacturing Corp. Vincent T. Finan, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Chrysler Corp. John B. Keenan, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corp. Robin H. Wendell, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Ford Motor Co. William Bellnier, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Ford Motor Co. Herbert S. Tompkins, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- General Motors Automobile Div., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad Robert P. Crisara, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- National Pneumatic Co. Inc. Holtzer-Cabot Div., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- N.Y.S. Dept. of Lab or - Div. of Research + Statistics - Abraham Lipp, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- N.Y.S. Decision of Placement and Unemployment Insurance, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- N.Y.S. Workmen's Compensation Board, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Textile Workers Union Jay E. Salzman, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Winchester Repeating Arms Co. Alfred P. D. Andrea Jr.+ Memos Misc., 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)